A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 1, Accession 2017:057 FA1317
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1966-1999; 3
  - Yale University - Consortium for Language Teaching and Learning, 1988-1996 (Box 80, Folder 596)
  - Yale University - Divinity School, 1971-1997 (Box 80, Folder 597-598)
  - Yale University - Peter Brooks Portrait Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 81, Folder 599)
  - Yale University Art Gallery - Eva Heese, 1989-1993 (Box 81, Folder 600)
  - Young Men's Christian Association for Greater New York, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 601)
  - The Youth Project, 1971-1974 (Box 81, Folder 602)
  - YMCA - Brooklyn Counseling Unit, 1968-1970 (Box 81, Folder 603)
  - YWCA - Centenary History, 1990-1995 (Box 81, Folder 604)
  - YWCA - National Board of the Executive Management Training Program, 1977-1980 (Box 81, Folder 605)
  - YWCA of the City of New York - Flushing Outreach Program, 1988-1995 (Box 81, Folder 606)
- Scholarships in American Art, 1982-1993; 4
  - Addison Gallery of Art, 1983-1990 (Box 91, Folder 679)
  - Brooklyn Museum of Art - Culin Collection, 1985-1991 (Box 91, Folder 680)
  - Carnegie Institute Museum of Art - Pre-1945 American Art, 1985-1993 (Box 91, Folder 681)
  - Sterling and Francine Clark Art Institute, 1982-1993 (Box 91, Folder 682)
  - Cleveland Museum - American Silver, 1982-1985 (Box 91, Folder 683)
  - Corcoran Gallery - James Peele, 1984-1991 (Box 91, Folder 684)
  - Detroit Institute of Art - American Paintings Volume 1, 1982-1992 (Box 92, Folder 685)
  - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art, 1982-1983 (Box 92, Folder 686)
  - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art - William Macbeth, 1983-1993 (Box 92, Folder 687)
  - Houston Museum of Fine Arts, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 688)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art - Catalog of American Art, 1982-1991 (Box 92, Folder 689)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art - Childe Hassam Flag Paintings, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 690)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art - Thomas Barrow, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 691)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art - Rococo Furniture, 1985-1995 (Box 92, Folder 692)
  - Museum of Modern Art - Mies Ven der Rohe, 1985-1990 (Box 92, Folder 693)
  - New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1982-1986 (Box 92, Folder 694-696)
  - New Museum of Contemporary Art - Anthology Artists Writings, 1984-1987 (Box 92, Folder 697)
  - New York Historical Society - Luman Reed, 1985-1990 (Box 93, Folder 698-699)
  - New York Historical Society - Thomas Hiram Hotchkiss, 1986-1994 (Box 93, Folder 700)
  - Toledo Museum of Art, 1982-1995 (Box 93, Folder 701-702)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum - Pre-1945 American Paintings, 1983-1996 (Box 93, Folder 704-705)
  - Whitney Museum of Art - Connoisseurship of Art in Europe, 1985-1988 (Box 94, Folder 706)
  - Whitney Museum of Art - European Collection, 1982-1996 (Box 94, Folder 707)
  - Winterthur Museum, 1982-1985 (Box 94, Folder 708)
  - Yale University Art Gallery - American Sculpture, 1985-1988 (Box 94, Folder 709)